<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>Mexican NLP Summer School 2021</title>
    
    
    <description>Mexican NLP Summer School 2021</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Live streaming on YouTube</title>
        <description>
          Links to YouTube channels - 
          To all participants that will not be able to join the zoom meeting, we are glad to inform you that all the activities from the Mexican NLP Summer School will be live-streamed through the channels of the AMPLN. Please take note of the channels. One channel can be fount here...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-05-31-ImportantNews/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-05-31-ImportantNews/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Program changes.</title>
        <description>
          New Tutorial Info! - 
          Dr. Alexander Gelbukh, and Dr. Grigori Sidorov, Full-time professors at the CIC-IPN Mexico, have agreed to give an introductory tutorial on Natural Language Processing. Dr. Gelbukh and Dr. Sidorov are highly influential researchers, members of one of the strongest and most traditional NLP groups in Mexico. Do not miss the...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-05-26-ProgramChanges/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-05-26-ProgramChanges/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Twitter account!</title>
        <description>
          Do not miss all the relevant information! - 
          We have created a dedicated Twiter account for the Mexican NLP Summer School 2021@NAACL 2021.
Do not miss all the relevant information, news, pics, and especially, get to know all the NLP community that will be participating in this great event!

Follow us at @EscuelaPLNMex!

        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-05-17-NewTwitter/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-05-17-NewTwitter/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Registration is now open!</title>
        <description>
          Registration information - 
          Registration for the Virtual Mexican NLP Summer School 2021@NAACL 2021 is now open. Our compromise is to keep the Summer School free and easily accessible. Therefore, no registration fees are considered. However, we have a limited number of simultaneous online participants, which is why we encourage all interested persons to...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-04-27-Registration/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-04-27-Registration/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Check out the amazing program</title>
        <description>
          Registration will be open soon! - 
          The Mexican NLP Summer School 2021 is currently scheduled to take place online from June 2nd to June 4th, 2021. All the activities are programmed in Mexico’s local timezone (GMT-5) You can see the full program here, and also don’t forget to read all the information regarding speakers, talks, and...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-04-26-FinalProgram/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-04-26-FinalProgram/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Mexican NLP Summer School 2021 will be fully virtual.</title>
        <description>
          Stay tuned for all the details! - 
          As you might already know, NAACL2021 is going virtual this year, check it out here. In accordance with this decision, the organization committee of the Mexican NLP Summer school has decided to follow the same modality. We’ll share final the details, including the program and registration process, in the coming...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-03-30-OnlineModality/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-03-30-OnlineModality/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to our new sponsor!!!</title>
        <description>
          Thanks to Bloomberg Engineering! - 
          We are very happy to announce that Bloomberg Engineering have decided to support our summer school, thanks!!! Are you looking for work opportunities or are you curious about what is being needed in the industry? This could be your opportunity to solve your doubts, there will be a special session...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-03-24-newSponsorBloomberg/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-03-24-newSponsorBloomberg/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to our new sponsors!!!</title>
        <description>
          The Mexican Consortium of AI and the SMIA got on board! - 
          We are very glad to announce that the Mexican Consortium of Artificial Intelligence CONACyT and the Mexican Society of Artificial Intelligence (SMIA), have decided to support our summer school. We are preparing really nice surprises,  thanks for the support!!!

Check out all the participant institutions here.

        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-02-25-newSponsors/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-02-25-newSponsors/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mexican NLP Summer School 2021 in conjunction with NAACL 2021</title>
        <description>
          Preparation for the school’s 2021 edition has already begun - 
          We are very excited about the next NLP Summer School 2021, to be held jointly with one of the most important NLP conferences in America, NAACL 2021

        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-12-10-first/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-12-10-first/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
